□ +1 (416) 578-7943 | ■ anish@hey.com | ♠ https://anishs.xyz/ | 🛅 anish5 | 🖸 git-anish

SUMMARY_

I'm an entrepreneur, and a bio-medical engineer. I founded and led SWFTCharge, which I successfully exited. Since the exit I travelled extensively, and have been consulting entrepreneurs on their ventures, and products. I most recently joined Skylight to help grow their new product lines and partnerships following their Series A. I believe my skillset is uniquely suited for a career in Product Management.

SKILLS.

Strategy

Business Product Management, Enterprise Software, Customer Interviews, Business Intelligence Software Google Cloud Suite, GApps, Adobe Creative Suite, Excel, MATLAB, InvisionApp, Balsamiq

Design Design Thinking, User Experience Design, User Interface Design, Mobile Design

Technology C, RobotC, SQL, IOS - TCL, ACL, Apple Script, Bash Script, Python, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, LaTeX

Cross Functional Team Lead, Stakeholder Management, User Stories, Product Lifecycle, Product Roadmap, Project

Planning, Lean Startup, A/B Testing, Quantitative Data Analysis, Profit & Loss, Forecasting

EXPERIENCE_

PRODUCT MANAGER (SENIOR GENERALIST - GROWTH & PRODUCT)

2019 - 2020

Skylight Tools Inc.

Skylight is focused on using technology to reimagine the home renovation experience. At Skylight I worked with the management team to create new sales channels, internal processes, and launch new product offerings.

- Created stakeholder consensus across the organization's leadership and various teams, projecting the value-added by launching new product offerings and limiting scope
 - Skylight Recommended reduced the time it takes to begin construction by up to 4 weeks or 25% compared to our standard offering. Thereby, offering our clients a fast and easy renovation process.
 - · Operationalized our Material Bank partnership allowing us to deliver renovation material samples to a client's home overnight. This partnership will eventually lead to eliminate the need for clients to visit any showrooms.
- Streamlined the product execution process for our clients and internal teams allowing for an increase in capacity of concurrent projects
 - Improved the client deliverable definitions of our renovation visualizations. Through this funnel iteration, we delivered faster turnaround times for the 3D renders of a proposed renovation. Improving key KPIs.
- Developed analytics dashboards based on critical KPIs to visualize project P&L
- · Converged internal data sources to forecast future material sample orders based on projected growth and demand

PRODUCT LEAD & CO-FOUNDER

2016 - 2018

SWFTCharge Inc. (Successfully Exited)

I launched and led this venture from the time it was a product focused company to our pivot into a service based company. We recognized the market need after conducting hundreds of customer interviews and executed plans to launch our self-funded MVP in Canada. After generating significant revenues through our MVP, I led our funding round to raise \$500,000 through angel investors to expand the company across various music festivals in North America and beyond.

- Developed and launched a service focused on eliminating battery anxiety at large scale events (Electric Forest, Coachella, Lost Lands, Boots & Hearts, etc.)
 - SWFTCharge provides access to wire free charging devices that allow users to keep their phones charged throughout the duration of a multiday event.
- Continuously adapted the business model and the service based on customer needs as well as stakeholder requirements
- Negotiated multi-year exclusive contracts with multinational corporations that operate events to secure our sales channel
- Increased revenue 6x YOY using the resources secured through the funding round
- · Created the logistics and operations roadmap to support events happening concurrently across North America

EDUCATION_

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING (BIOMEDICAL)

2013 - 2017

Queen's University, Kingston, Ontario, Canada

AVOCATIONAL ACTIVITIES ___

DUE DILIGENCE LEAD

York Angels Investors

The York Angel Investors is Canada's largest group of angel investors with a broad range of professional experience. I previously received a term sheet from YAI for my own venture and have since joined the group to assist investors through the due diligence process.

Worked on developing the due diligence process and conducted due diligence for incoming investment opportunities

WINNER & FINALIST

The Next 36: Wearable Tech Hackathon hosted by Google

- Combined the functionality of both the Myo (Thalmic Labs) and the MeU to create the 'NightHawk' in under 12 hours
- Created an application to automate transit terminal transactions using the Nymi bracelet, and a MasterCard API
- Videos showcasing the ideas, and other project details are available on my LinkedIn page